<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
	<entry key="summary.content.summary.help"><![CDATA[
<div id="helpmain">
	<h3>Resource summary</h3>
	<p>The resource summary page is used to view, comment and rate a resource. Resource owners and content managers	can also manage resources and resource versions.</p>
	<p>The main panel of the summary displays resource content, viewing options, ratings and comments.</p> 
	<p>Select a resource then a viewer option to display the resource.</p>
	<p>Select a rating, enter a comment then select <b>ADD COMMENT</b> to rate the resource.</p>
	<p>Actions, further information and previous versions can be accessed using the <b>Details</b> and <b>Actions</b> area links.	
	<ul>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('moreAction')">More about the Actions links...</a></li>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('moreDetails')">More about the Details links...</a></li>
	</ul> 
	<div style="clear: both;"></div>
	<h3>Other page features</h3>
	<ul>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('moreNavigation')">More about the Navigation menu...</a></li>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('moreAddRemoveFavourites')">More about Add/Remove favourites...</a></li>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('moreShare')">More about Share with others... </a></li>
	</ul>
	<div style="clear: both;"></div>
</div>
	]]></entry>
	<entry key="summary.content.versions.help"><![CDATA[
<div id="helpmain">
	<h3>Versions</h3>
	<p>The Versions page displays a list of resource versions and is accessible from the resource summary page.</p>
	<p>The main panel displays all previous versions of the resource and their status. Select a previous version to display the resource summary page for that version.</p>
	<br>
	<h3>Other page features</h3>
	<ul>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('moreNavigation')">More about the Navigation menu...</a></li>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('moreAddRemoveFavourites')">More about Add/Remove favourites...</a></li>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('moreShare')">More about Share with others... </a></li>
	</ul>
	<div style="clear: both;"></div>
	<ul>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('moreDetails')">More about Details links...</a></li>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('moreAction')">More about Actions links...</a></li>
	</ul>
	<div style="clear: both;"></div>
</div>
	]]></entry>
	<entry key="summary.content.help"><![CDATA[
<div id="moreAction" style="display: none">
	<h3>More about Actions links...</h3> 
	<p>The Actions area can display the following actions:</p>
	<ul>
		<li><b>Modify key resource</b>  &mdash;  this link can be used to modfiy the resource as a key resource to one or more hierarchy topics.</li>
		<li><b>Edit this version</b>  &mdash;  this link displays the resource details in a contribution wizard for editing. Saving changes updates the current resource version.</li>
		<li><b>Create a new version</b>  &mdash;  this link displays a contribution wizard populated with resource data. Complete the wizard to create a new version.</li>
		<li><b>Redraft this version</b>  &mdash;  this link allows the resource to re-enter the workflow. It is intended for resources that were rejected prior to workflow completion.</li>
		<li><b>New contribution of same type</b>  &mdash;  this link displays a blank contribution wizard for the same collection as the original resource. Complete the wizard to create a new resource.</li>
		<li><b>Clone item into a collection</b>  &mdash;  this link can be used to copy resources between collections. It can accept a suitable XSLT for transforming current resource metadata to that required for the new collection. This operation does not change the original resource.</li>
		<li><b>Move item into another collection</b>  &mdash;  this link can be used to transfer a resource between collections. It can accept a suitable XSLT for transforming current resource metadata to that required for the new collection.</li>
		<li><b>Archive this version</b>  &mdash;  this link removes the resource from search results and any associated workflow.</li>
		<li><b>Suspend this version</b>  &mdash;  this link temporarily removes resources from search results and is intended for content that is temporarily unavailable.</li>
		<li><b>Delete this version</b>  &mdash;  this link removes the resource from the repository.</li>
		<li><b>Change ownership</b>  &mdash;  this link can be used to share the resource with collaborators or change resource owner.</li>
		<li><b>Export</b>  &mdash;  this link displays the Export page where export options are displayed.</li>
	</ul>
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('helpmain')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>

<div id="moreDetails" style="display: none">
	<h3>More about the Details links...</h3> 
	<p>The Details area displays information about the resource including:</p>
	<ul>
		<li><b>Owner</b>  &mdash;  displays the owner of the resource.</li>
		<li><b>Collection</b>  &mdash;  select this link to display a list of all resources in the same collection as the current resource.</li>
		<li><b>Collaborators</b>  &mdash;  displays the users selected as collaborators for the resource.</li>
		<li><b>Version</b>  &mdash;  displays the resource version. Select the (show all) link to display the Versions page.</li>
		<li><b>Status</b>  &mdash;  displays the resource’s status.</li>
		<li><b>Moderation history</b>  &mdash;  select this link to display the History page with a list of history details.</li>
		<li><b>Moderation progress</b>  &mdash;  select this link to display the Moderation progress page.</li>
		<li><b>Activations</b>  &mdash;  select this link to display the Activations page with a list of all activations.</li>
		<li><b>Terms of use</b>  &mdash;  select this link to display the Terms of use page with terms and a list of users who have accepted those terms.</li>
	</ul>
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('helpmain')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>	

<div id="moreAddRemoveFavourites" style="display:none">
	<h3>More about Add/Remove favourites</h3> 
	<p>Resources can be added to your Favourites page for quick access.</p>
	<ul>
	<li><b>Add to favourites</b> &mdash; select this link to display the Add to favourites dialog where tags can be entered to simplify searching. Select the resource version to display in the favourites page:
	<ul>
	<li><b>Always use latest version</b> &mdash; select this option to use the latest version when the current version is superseded.</li>
	<li><b>This version</b> &mdash; select this option to use this version even when later versions are available.</li>
	</ul>
	</li>
	<li>Select ADD to add to your favourites resources list and return to the resource summary or CANCEL to return to the resource summary without creating a favourite.</li>
	<li><b>Remove from favourites</b> &mdash; select this link then OK to confirm, to remove this resource from your favourites resources list.</li>
	</ul>
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('helpmain')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>

<div id="moreShare" style="display: none">
	<h3>More about Share with others</h3>
	<p>Users can be emailed a resource access link or notified when the resource becomes publicly available.</p>
	<ul>
		<li><b>Share with others</b> &mdash; select this button to display the Share with others page where resource access or notifications can be configured.</li>
	</ul>
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('helpmain')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>

<div id="moreNavigation" style="display: none">
	<h3>More about the Navigation menu</h3>
	<p>The navigation menu is displayed on the left-hand side of the page and displays links for accessing and managing content. The menu comprises standard EQUELLA, browse, custom and administration links.
	The links displayed depend on the privileges granted by the System Administrator.</p>
	<ul> 
		<li><b>Standard links</b> &mdash; links for accessing content and can include Dashboard, Favourites, Search, My resources, Contribute.</li>
		<li><b>Browse links</b> &mdash; links for browsing EQUELLA topics. When more than five topics have been added the first four plus a <b>More...</b> link are displayed.</li>
		<li><b>Custom links</b> &mdash; links for commonly accessed content that can be within EQUELLA or an external website.</li>
		<li><b>Administration links</b> &mdash; links for managing or configuring EQUELLA that can include Tasks, Manage resources, Manage activations, Reporting, Settings. Select a navigation menu link to display the corresponding page.</li>
	</ul>
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('helpmain')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>
	]]></entry>
	<entry key="summary.content.summary.item.selection.summary.help"><![CDATA[
<div id="helpmain">
	<h3>Summary page</h3>
	<p>This page is used to select EQUELLA content for use in the integrated LMS. Content can be dragged and dropped to the required LMS section, or the required LMS section can be highlighted, then the select (plus) buttons used to add content to that section. Note that the LMS section that the EQUELLA selection session was accessed from will always be the default LMS section. Different sections can be selected by clicking in the yellow space around the section name.</p>
	<p>Summary pages can be added to an LMS section by dragging and dropping the resource title to the required section, or clicking the Select summary page button.</p>
	<p>Specific attachments can be added to an LMS section by dragging and dropping the attachment title to the required section, or clicking the plus button beside the required attachment.</p>
	<p>All attachments for a resource can be added to an LMS section by clicking the Select all button. This will result in a separate link for each attachment in the LMS section.</p>
	<p>All attachments for a resource can be added as a package to an LMS section by clicking the Select package button. This will result in one link in the LMS section, which, when selected, allows the user to view all the attachments within a 'package player'.</p>
	<p>Selections for one LMS section can be reviewed and edited by clicking the LMS section name link.</p>
	<p>All selections (across multiple LMS sections) can be reviewed and edited by clicking the Review all selections link.</p>
	<div style="clear: both;"></div>
</div>
	]]></entry>
	<entry key="summary.content.summary.item.selection.help"><![CDATA[
<div id="resourceSelect">
	<h3>Choose EQUELLA resources</h3>
	<p>Drag and drop resources to the required areas below or click the Select button to add the resource to the highlighted area. Click Save once selections are complete.</p>
	<div style="clear: both;"></div>
</div>
	]]></entry>
	<entry key="summary.content.summary.item.selection.details.help"><![CDATA[
<div id="helpmain">
	<h3>Details page</h3>
	<p>The Details tab displays further details of a resource as well as links to view other versions and moderation history. It also provides links to Actions that can be performed on the item (depending on user permissions), such as Edit, Clone, Delete etc. The available actions are the same as those on the EQUELLA resource summary page.</p>
	<ul>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('moreAction')">More about the Actions links...</a></li>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('moreDetails')">More about the Details links...</a></li>
	</ul> 
	<div style="clear: both;"></div>
</div>
	]]></entry>
</properties>
