<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
	<entry key="helppage"><![CDATA[

<div id="helpmain">

<h3>Dashboard</h3>
<p>
	The Dashboard page is your home page and displays a navigation menu, portlets, help and screen options. The menu and portlets can
	comprise personally configured and system administrator configured options.
</p>

<h3>Portlets</h3>
<p>
	Portlets are displayed in the central pane and typically display a summary of the available content and links to access that content. {3}
</p>

<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreonportals'')">More about portlets...</a></p>


<h3>Navigation menu</h3>
<p>
	The navigation menu is displayed on the left-hand side of the page and provides links for accessing content that include standard EQUELLA
	links and system links configured by the administrator. The links displayed depend on the privileges granted by the System Administrator.
</p>

<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreonnavlinks'')">More about navigation links...</a></p>

</div>

<div id="moreonportals" style="display: none">
<h3>Portlets</h3>
	<ul>
		<li>Move a portlet by dragging the portlet title bar.</li>
		<li>Show or hide portlet content by selecting the toggle <img src="{0}">
		 button on the left-hand side of the portlet title bar.</li>
		<li>Edit the portlet details by selecting the <img src="{1}"> button at the right-hand side of the portlet title bar.</li>
		<li>Close a portlet by selecting the <img src="{2}"> button at the right-hand side of the portlet title bar.</li>
		<li>Administer the portlets by selecting Settings from the navigation menu then Dashboard administration.</li>
	</ul>
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''helpmain'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>



<div id="moreonnavlinks" style="display: none">
	<h3>Navigation menu links</h3>
	<p>Navigation menu links can include:</p>
	<ul>
		<li><b>Standard links</b> &mdash; Dashboard, Search, Contribute, Favourites, My resources.</li>
		<li><b>Custom links</b> &mdash; Administrator configurable links that can be an alternative to a portlet when access to content is required. Add custom links to the navigation menu by selecting Settings from the navigation menu then Edit custom links.</li>
		<li><b>Administrator links</b> &mdash; Settings, Manage resources.</li>
	</ul>
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''helpmain'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>



	]]></entry>
	<entry key="enduser.noportlets.helptext"><![CDATA[
		<p>Select the <b>SCREEN OPTIONS</b> button to add portlets to the dashboard, an example is shown below.</p>
		<img src="{0}" alt="The screen options and help buttons can be found in the top right hand corner, after the page title">

		<p>To add an example <em>'Welcome'</em> portlet to be displayed to all EQUELLA users, complete the following:</p>
		<ol>
			<li>Select the <b>SCREEN OPTIONS</b> button to display a list of portlets.</li>
			<li>Select the <b>Formatted text</b> option to display the <b>Create portlet</b> page.</li>
			<li>Configure the details as required, an example is shown below:
				<ol>
					<li>Select to allow users to close or minimise the portlet as required.</li>
					<li>Select the <b>CHANGE</b> button to display the <b>Select recipients</b> dialog.</li>
					<li>Search for the users, groups or roles then select the <b>OK</b> button.</li>
					<li>
						Enter text in the HTML Editor pane.
						<img class="removetwoindentsfornoportal" src="{1}" alt="Enter any text with markup in the HTML Editor to have it displayed in the portal">
					</li>
					<li>Select the <b>SAVE</b> button to display the portlet on the user's Dashboard.</li>
				</ol>
			</li>
		</ol>]]>
	</entry>

	<entry key="enduser.noportlets.spiel"><![CDATA[
		<p>Select an option from the navigation menu to the left to use EQUELLA features.</p>
		<p>Select the <b>HELP</b> button to show or hide online help.</p>
	]]></entry>

	<entry key="sysuser.noportlets.spiel"><![CDATA[
		<p>When logging in with a System account, Dashboard portlets, <b>HELP</b> and <b>SCREEN OPTIONS</b> buttons, are not enabled for the Welcome/Dashboard screen.</p>
		<p>To modify or delete Dashboard portlets seen by non-admin EQUELLA users, choose Settings from the navigation menu then Dashboard administration.</p>
	]]></entry>


	<entry key="admin.help"><![CDATA[
		<div id="helpmain">
			<h3>Dashboard administration</h3>
			<p>The Dashboard administration page provides a portlet search that displays a list of all portlets used on dashboards with associated information.</p>
			<p>This page provides for portlet searching, viewing, sorting and filtering results with links to edit or delete a portlet.</p>
			<ul>
				<li>Search—enter search terms to display matching results.</li>
				<li>Portlet name—select the portlet name to display the portlet’s edit page.</li>
				<li>Actions—select an action to perform on the portlet.</li>
				<li>Filters—refine the search by filtering for criteria.</li>
			</ul>
			<ul>
				<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreoncriteria'')">More on search criteria...</a></li>
				<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreonfilter'')">More on the Filter box...</a></li>
				<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreonnavlinks'')">More about navigation links...</a></li>
			</ul>
    		<div style="clear: both;"></div>
		</div>

		<div id="moreoncriteria" style="display: none">
			<h3>Search criteria</h3>
			<ul>
				<li><b>Search</b> &mdash; enter search terms.</li>
				<li><b>search</b> &mdash; select this button or press the Enter key to display items that match the search criteria.</li>
			</ul>
			<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''helpmain'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
		</div>

		<div id="moreonfilter" style="display: none">
			<h3>Filter box</h3>
			<p>The filter box provides options for reducing the number of displayed results. Select the  <img src="{0}"> toggle button to maximise or minimise the portlet.</p>
			<ul>
				<li><b>Filter by Owner</b> &mdash; select the <b>select user</b> button to display the <b>Select owner to filter by</b> dialog where owners can be found by name search then selected to filter the search results.</li>
				<li><b>Filter by type</b> &mdash; expand the drop-down menu to choose to a specific portlet type, or choose the default option All portlets.</li>
				<li><b>Filter by visibility</b> &mdash; expand the drop-down menu to choose to view portlets that are viewable to others, user portlets, or all portlets.</li>
			</ul>
			<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''helpmain'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
		</div>

		<div id="moreonnavlinks" style="display: none">
			<h3>Navigation menu</h3>
			<p>
				The navigation menu is displayed on the left-hand side of the page and display links for accessing content that include standard EQUELLA
				links and system links configured by the administrator. The links displayed depend on the privileges granted by the System Administrator.
			</p>
			<p>Navigation menu links can include:</p>
			<ul>
				<li><b>Standard links</b> &mdash; Dashboard, Search, Contribute, Favourites, My resources.</li>
				<li><b>Custom links</b> &mdash; Administrator configurable links that can be an alternative to a portlet when access to content is required. Add custom links to the navigation menu by selecting Settings from the navigation menu then Edit custom links.</li>
				<li><b>Administrator links</b> &mdash; Settings, Manage resources.</li>
			</ul>
			<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''helpmain'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
		</div>
	]]></entry>
</properties>
