<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
	<entry key="help.list"><![CDATA[
<div id="helpmain">
	<h3>Existing links</h3>
	<p>The Existing links page displays a list of existing custom links showing the display text, URL and link icon.</p>
	<p>Select to <b>add</b> a new link, alternatively <b>edit</b> or <b>delete</b> an existing link. Listed links can be reordered by dragging a link to a new position in the list.</p>
	<ul>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('moreAdd')">More on editing or adding a link...</a></li>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('moreonnavlinks')">More about the Navigation menu...</a></li>
	</ul>
    <div style="clear: both;"></div>
</div>

<div id="moreAdd" style="display: none">
	<h3>Editing or adding a link</h3>
	<p>Links are displayed in the order they appear on the user menu and the following options are provided to manage the links:<p>
	<ul>
		<li><b>edit</b> &mdash; displays the <b>Edit link details</b> page</li>
		<li><b>delete</b> &mdash; removes the link from the list after confirmation.</li>
		<li><b>add</b> &mdash; display the <b>Add a new link</b> page</li>
		<li>Drag a listed link &mdash; moves the link to a new position in the list, providing a method of reordering the list.</li>
	</ul>
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('helpmain')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>
	
<div id="moreonnavlinks" style="display: none">
		<h3>Navigation menu</h3>
	<p>
		The navigation menu is displayed on the left-hand side of the page and display links for accessing content that include standard EQUELLA
		links and system links configured by the administrator. The links displayed depend on the privileges granted by the System Administrator.
	</p>
	
	<p>Navigation menu links can include:</p>
	<ul>
		<li><b>Standard links</b> &mdash; Dashboard, Search, Contribute, Favourites, My resources.</li>
		<li><b>Custom links</b> &mdash; Administrator configurable links that can be an alternative to a portlet when access to content is required. Add custom links to the navigation menu by selecting Settings from the navigation menu then Edit custom links.</li>
		<li><b>Administrator links</b> &mdash; Settings, Manage resources.</li>
	</ul>
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('helpmain')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>

	]]></entry>
	
	
	<entry key="help.edit"><![CDATA[
<div id="helpmain">
	<h3>Edit custom links</h3>
	<p>The Edit custom link page is used to reconfigure an existing custom link.</p>
	<p>Enter <b>Display text</b>, a relative or absolute <b>URL</b> then <b>select users</b>, groups or roles that can access the link. Once added the page must be refreshed (F5) to see the added link.</p>
	
	<ul>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('moreEdit')">More on editing or adding a link...</a></li>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('moreonnavlinks')">More about the Navigation menu...</a></li>
	</ul>
    <div style="clear: both;"></div>
</div>

<div id="moreEdit"  style="display: none">
	<h3>Editing or adding a link</h3>
	<p>A custom link can have the following properties:<p>
	<ul>
		<li><b>Display text</b> &mdash; enter the name of the link to be displayed to users.</li>
		<li><b>URL</b> &mdash; enter an absolute or relative URL. Relative URLs will be resolved by appending to the server’s URL (e.g. '/fieldwork/report_writing.html' will become 'http://equella.myequellainstitution.edu/fieldwork/report_writing.html'.</li>
		<li><b>Open in a new window</b> &mdash; check this checkbox to display the URL in a new browser window.</li>
		<li><b>Who can view this URL</b> &mdash; click the <b>select users...</b> button to display the <b>Select recipients</b> dialog where users can be selected.</li>
		<li><b>Upload an icon</b> &mdash; <b>browse</b> to then select the icon file. <b>upload</b> the icon to EQUELLA and display it on this page at the icon size.</li>
		<li><b>download</b> &mdash; select this button to download the icon used at the entered URL. </li>
		<li><b>remove icon</b> &mdash; select this button to remove the displayed icon.</li>
		<li><b>save</b> &mdash; save any changes to this link and return to the custom links page.</li>
		<li><b>cancel</b> &mdash; discard any changes and return to the custom links page.</li>
	</ul>
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('helpmain')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>

<div id="moreonnavlinks" style="display: none">
	<h3>Navigation menu</h3>
	<p>
		The navigation menu is displayed on the left-hand side of the page and display links for accessing content that include standard EQUELLA
		links and system links configured by the administrator. The links displayed depend on the privileges granted by the System Administrator.
	</p>
	
	<p>Navigation menu links can include:</p>
	<ul>
		<li><b>Standard links</b> &mdash; Dashboard, Search, Contribute, Favourites, My resources.</li>
		<li><b>Custom links</b> &mdash; Administrator configurable links that can be an alternative to a portlet when access to content is required. Add custom links to the navigation menu by selecting Settings from the navigation menu then Edit custom links.</li>
		<li><b>Administrator links</b> &mdash; Settings, Manage resources.</li>
	</ul>
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('helpmain')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>

	]]></entry>
</properties>
