<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>

<entry key="themesettingshelp">
<![CDATA[
<div id="themeMain" >
	<h3>Theme settings page</h3>
	<p>The Theme settings page is used to change the <i>‘look and feel’</i> of the EQUELLA institution.</p>
	<p>Select <b>browse</b> to choose a new theme file then <b>upload</b> to change the EQUELLA theme.  Theme files comprise a ZIP archive of 
	 images and style sheets overriding those from EQUELLA. It is important that image and style sheet names are identical to the existing names
	 for the correct display of the theme.</p>
	<ul>
		<li><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreNavigation'')">More about the Navigation menu...</a></li>
	</ul>
</div>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key="commonmoredivs">
<![CDATA[
<div id="moreNavigation" style="display: none">
	<h3>More about the Navigation menu</h3>
	<p>The navigation menu is displayed on the left-hand side of the page and displays links for accessing and managing content. The menu comprises standard EQUELLA, browse, custom and administration links.
	The links displayed depend on the privileges granted by the System Administrator.</p>
	<ul> 
		<li><b>Standard links</b> &mdash; links for accessing content and can include Dashboard, Favourites, Search, My resources, Contribute.</li>
		<li><b>Browse links</b> &mdash; links for browsing EQUELLA topics. When more than five topics have been added the first four plus a <b>More...</b> link are displayed.</li>
		<li><b>Custom links</b> &mdash; links for commonly accessed content that can be within EQUELLA or an external website.</li>
		<li><b>Administration links</b> &mdash; links for managing or configuring EQUELLA that can include Tasks, Manage resources, Manage activations, Reporting, Settings.
		Select a navigation menu link to display the corresponding page.</li>
	</ul>
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''themeMain'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>	

]]>
</entry>
</properties>