<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>	
	<entry key="searchsettings.settings.help"><![CDATA[
<div id="helpMain" >
	<h3>Search settings</h3>
	<p>The Search settings page is used to configure the <b>Filter</b> and <b>Sort</b> boxes that appear on the Search pages.</p>
	<p>The default sorting can be configured and search filters based on resource MIME type can be configured and removed.</p>
	<ul>
		<li><b>Default results order</b> &mdash; select the default ordering option from the drop-down list.</li>
		<li><b>Show the ‘Include non-live items’ checkbox</b> &mdash; check this checkbox to include any items that don’t have a Live status in the search results.</li>
		<li><b>Generate authenticated RSS and Atom feeds by default</b> &mdash; check this checkbox to require an active EQUELLA session to view RSS and Atom feeds of the search results.</li>
		<li><b>Add a new search filter</b> &mdash; select this button to display the Create new search filter page.</li>
		<li><b>Search filter name</b> &mdash; select the filter name (or click the Edit link) to display the Edit search filter page.</li>
		<li><b>Remove</b> &mdash; select this link to remove the filter after confirmation of the action.</li>
	</ul>	
	<br>
	<h3>Other page features</h3>
	<ul>
		<li><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('moreNavigation')">More about the Navigation menu...</a></li>
	</ul>
</div>
	]]></entry>
	<entry key="searchsettings.editfilter.help"><![CDATA[
<div id="helpMain" >
	<h3>Edit search filter</h3>
	<p>The Edit search filter page is used to configure MIME type filters for search results.</p>
	<p>Enter a <b>Name</b> then select MIME types from the list to create a filter that will display only resources of the selected MIME types in the search results.</p>
	<ul>
		<li><b>Name</b> &mdash; enter a name to distinguish the filter.</li>
		<li><b>MIME types</b> &mdash; check at least one MIME type.</li>
		<li><b>Save</b> &mdash; select this button to display the Search settings page and save any changes to filter.</li>
		<li><b>Cancel</b> &mdash; select this button to return to the Search settings page without saving the changes to the filter.</li>
	</ul>	
	<br>
	<h3>Other page features</h3>
	<ul>
		<li><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('moreNavigation')">More about the Navigation menu...</a></li>
	</ul>
</div>
	]]></entry>
	<entry key="helppage.moreNavigation"><![CDATA[
<div id="moreNavigation" style="display: none">
	<h3>More about the Navigation menu</h3>
	<p>The navigation menu is displayed on the left-hand side of the page and displays links for accessing and managing content. The menu comprises standard EQUELLA, browse, custom and administration links.
	The links displayed depend on the privileges granted by the System Administrator.</p>
	<ul> 
		<li><b>Standard links</b> &mdash; links for accessing content and can include Dashboard, Favourites, Search, My resources, Contribute.</li>
		<li><b>Browse links</b> &mdash; links for browsing EQUELLA topics. When more than five topics have been added the first four plus a <b>More...</b> link are displayed.</li>
		<li><b>Custom links</b> &mdash; links for commonly accessed content that can be within EQUELLA or an external website.</li>
		<li><b>Administration links</b> &mdash; links for managing or configuring EQUELLA that can include Tasks, Manage resources, Manage activations, Reporting, Settings.
		Select a navigation menu link to display the corresponding page.</li>
	</ul>
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText('helpMain')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>
	]]></entry>
</properties>
