<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
	<entry key="main"><![CDATA[
<div id="main" >
	<h3>Manage resources</h3>
	
	<p>The Manage resources page provides functionality for managing multiple resources.  To manage resources enter search criteria, select resources from the  
	results then select the Perform an action button to display the Bulk Actions dialog.  Choose then EXECUTE an action.</p>

	<ul>
		<li><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreSearchTerms'')">More on search criteria...</a></li>
		<li><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreSearchResults'')">More on search results...</a></li>
		<li><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreSelection'')">More on selection...</a></li>
		<li><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreCowbell'')">More on performing an action...</a></li>
		<li><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreShare'')">More about Share search query...</a></li>
	</ul>
	
	<br>
	<h3>Other page features</h3>
	
	<ul>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreNavigation'')">More about the Navigation menu...</a></li>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreSortBox'')">More on the Sort box...</a></li>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreFilterBox'')">More on the Filter box...</a></li>
	</ul>
	<div style="clear: both;"></div>
</div>
	]]></entry>
	
	<entry key="moreSearchTerms"><![CDATA[
<div id="moreSearchTerms" style="display:none;">
	<h3>More on search criteria</h3>
	
	<ul>
		<li><b>Search</b> &mdash; enter search terms.
		<li><b>Within</b> &mdash; select a collection or system wide search from the drop-down list.
		<li><button id="searchform-search" class="btn btn-primary add-on btn-equella btn-mini" type="button" style="display: inline-block"><i class="icon-search icon-white"></i>
</button> &mdash; select this button or press the Enter key to display items that match the search criteria.
	</ul>
	
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>
	]]></entry>
	
	<entry key="moreSearchResults"><![CDATA[
<div id="moreSearchResults" style="display:none;">
	<h3>More on search results</h3>
	
	<p>The information displayed comprises:</p>
	
	<ul>
		<li><b>Item title (e.g EQUELLA Training Guide)</b> &mdash; select this link to display the item</li>
		<li><b>&lt;x> comments</b> &mdash; select this link to display the comment dialog where an item comment can be entered.</li>
		<li><b>Add to favourites</b> &mdash; select this link to add the item to the favourites list.</li>
	</ul>
	
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>
	]]></entry>

	<entry key="moreSelection"><![CDATA[
<div id="moreSelection" style="display: none">
	<h3>More on selection</h3>
	
	<p>The selection panel enables selection and viewing of all resources appearing in the results list. The displayed links include:</p>
	
	<ul>
		<li><b>View selected items</b> &mdash; displays a dialog with a list of all selected resources. Deselect resources from this dialog by selecting the resource''s 
			<img src="{0}" alt="Remove"> button. CLOSE the dialog to return to the Manage resources page. 
			This link is only displayed when resources have been selected.</li>
		<li><b>Unselect all items</b> &mdash; deselects all selected resources. This link is only displayed when resources have been selected.</li>
		<li><b>Select all items in this search</b> &mdash; selects all resources in the results list.</li>
	</ul>
	
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>
	]]></entry>
	
	<entry key="moreActions"><![CDATA[
<div id="moreCowbell" style="display: none">
	<h3>More on performing an action</h3>
	
	<p>An action is performed on all the selected resources. Actions requiring multiple steps will 
	enable the <button class="btn btn-equella"><i class="icon-arrow-left icon-white"></i> Prev</button> and <button class="btn btn-equella">Next <i class="icon-arrow-right icon-white"></i></button> buttons for entry of further action information.</p>
	
	<ul>
		<li><b>Choose an action to perform</b> &mdash; select an action from the drop-down list. Actions requiring multiple steps will enable the <button class="btn btn-equella">Next <i class="icon-arrow-right icon-white"></i></button> button.</li>
		<li><b>Selected resource list</b> &mdash; displays all selected resources. Select the <img src="{0}" alt="Remove"> button to remove the resource from this list.</li>
		<li><button class="btn btn-equella"><i class="icon-arrow-left icon-white"></i> Prev</button> &mdash; select this button to return to the previous step in a multi-step action.</li>
		<li><button class="btn btn-success"><i class="icon-ok icon-white"></i> Execute</button> &mdash; select this button to perform the selected action.</li>
		<li><button class="btn btn-equella">Next <i class="icon-arrow-right icon-white"></i></button> &mdash; select this button to display the next step in a multi-step action.</li>
	</ul>
	
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>
	]]></entry>
	
	<entry key="moreShare"><![CDATA[
<div id="moreShare" style="display: none">
	<h3>More about Share search query</h3>
	
	<p>Search results can be shared with other users by sending them the search query for their use.</p>
	
	<ul>
		<li>
			<b>Share search query</b> &mdash; select this button to display the <b>Share search query</b> dialog where results can be shared by:
			<ul>
				<li><b>RSS or Atom feed</b> &mdash; copy these options to a feed reader to be notified when the results list changes for this search.</li>
				<li><b>Share search results via URL</b> &mdash; copy the displayed link URL to a document or email to share. When selected this link will require the user to log into EQUELLA to view the search results.</li>
				<li><b>Share search results via email</b> &mdash; enter an email address to send the search results by email to other users. <b>Check the Share only results viewable by guests</b> when sending to non-EQUELLA users. </li>
				<li>Select <img src="{0}" alt="Close"> to close the dialog and display the results page.</li>	
			</ul>
		</li>
	</ul>
	
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>
	]]></entry>
	
	<entry key="moreNavigation"><![CDATA[
<div id="moreNavigation" style="display:none;">
	<h3>More about the Navigation menu</h3>
	
	<p>The navigation menu is displayed on the left-hand side of the page and displays links for accessing and managing content. The menu comprises standard EQUELLA, browse, custom and administration links.
	The links displayed depend on the privileges granted by the System Administrator.</p>
	
	<ul> 
		<li><b>Standard links</b> &mdash; links for accessing content and can include Dashboard, Favourites, Search, My resources, Contribute.</li>
		<li><b>Browse links</b> &mdash; links for browsing EQUELLA topics. When more than five topics have been added the first four plus a <b>More...</b> link are displayed.</li>
		<li><b>Custom links</b> &mdash; links for commonly accessed content that can be within EQUELLA or an external website.</li>
		<li><b>Administration links</b> &mdash; links for managing or configuring EQUELLA that can include Tasks, Manage resources, Manage activations, Reporting, Settings.
		Select a navigation menu link to display the corresponding page.</li>
	</ul>
	 
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>

</div>
	]]></entry>
	
	<entry key="moreSortBox"><![CDATA[
<div id="moreSortBox" style="display:none;">
	<h3>More on the Sort box</h3>
	
	<p>The Sort box provides options for sorting results lists. Select the <img src="{0}" alt="Minimise / Maximise"> toggle button to maximise or minimise the box.</p>
	
	<ul>
		<li><b>Sort results by</b> &mdash; select an option from the drop-down list to change the sort order.</li>
		<li><b>Reverse order of results</b> &mdash; check this checkbox to reverse the default sort order e.g. reverses a Title ordering from A-Z to Z-A.</li>
	</ul>
	
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>
	]]></entry>
	
	<entry key="moreFilterBox"><![CDATA[
<div id="moreFilterBox" style="display:none;">
	<h3>More on the Filter box</h3>
	
	<p>The filter box provides options for reducing the number of displayed results. Select the <img src="{0}" alt="Minimise / Maximise"> toggle button to maximise or minimise the box.
	Multiple filters can be applied and can include the following filters:</p>
	
	<ul>
		<li><b>Filter by owner</b> &mdash; select the <b>SELECT USER</b> button to display the <b>Select owner to filter by</b> 
			dialog where owners can be found by name search then selected to filter the search results. 
			Select the CHANGE USER button to change the owner selected or select the CLEAR button to remove.</li>
		<li><b>Filter by date modified</b> &mdash; select an option from the drop-down list then enter or select a date. Select <b>Clear</b> to remove the date filter.</li>
		<li><b>Filter by status</b> &mdash; select an option from the drop-down list to display results with the selected status.</li>			
	</ul>
	
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>
	]]></entry>
</properties>
