<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<entry key="main"><![CDATA[
<div id="main" >
	<h3>MIME type editor</h3>
	
	<p>The MIME type editor page by default displays a list of all file MIME types and associated file extensions. 
	MIME types are used to distinguish different file types.</p>
	
	<p>To refine the MIME type list:</p>
	
	<ul>
		<li>Enter a term in the Search field then select Search to display the list of MIME types matching the entered term.</li>
	</ul>
	
	<p>MIME types can be created, edited and deleted from this page.  <a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreMime'')">More on MIME types...</a></p>
	
	<br>
	<h3>Other page features</h3>
	 		 
	<ul>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreNavigation'')">More about the Navigation menu...</a></li>
	</ul>
	<div style="clear: both;"></div>
</div>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key="moreMime">
<![CDATA[
<div id="moreMime" style="display:none;">
	<h3>More on MIME types</h3>
	
	<p>To edit an existing MIME type:</p>
	<ul> 
		<li>Select the MIME type link, or alternatively select the <button class="btn btn-equella btn-mini"><i class="icon-pencil icon-white"></i> Edit</button> button, to display the Edit MIME type page.</li>
	</ul>
	
	<p>To add a new MIME type:</p>
	<ul> 
		<li>Select the <input class="add-mime action-button" type="button" value="Add MIME type" style="width: 200px"> button to display the Add MIME type page.</li>
	</ul>
	
	<p>To delete an existing MIME type:</p>
	<ul> 
		<li>Select the <button class="btn btn-warning btn-mini"><i class="icon-remove icon-white"></i> Delete</button> button immediately below the MIME type.</li>
		<li>Confirm the action to delete the MIME type from EQUELLA.</li>
	</ul>
	 
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>
]]>
</entry>


<entry key="moreNavigation">
<![CDATA[
<div id="moreNavigation" style="display:none;">
	<h3>More about the Navigation menu</h3>
	
	<p>The navigation menu is displayed on the left-hand side of the page and displays links for accessing and managing content. The menu comprises standard EQUELLA, browse, custom and administration links.
	The links displayed depend on the privileges granted by the System Administrator.</p>
	
	<ul> 
		<li><b>Standard links</b> &mdash; links for accessing content and can include Dashboard, Favourites, Search, My resources, Contribute.</li>
		<li><b>Browse links</b> &mdash; links for browsing EQUELLA topics. When more than five topics have been added the first four plus a <b>More...</b> link are displayed.</li>
		<li><b>Custom links</b> &mdash; links for commonly accessed content that can be within EQUELLA or an external website.</li>
		<li><b>Administration links</b> &mdash; links for managing or configuring EQUELLA that can include Tasks, Manage resources, Manage activations, Reporting, Settings.
		Select a navigation menu link to display the corresponding page.</li>
	</ul>
	 
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key="mainEdit">
<![CDATA[
<div id="main" >
	<h3>Edit MIME type</h3>
	
	<p>The Edit MIME type page displays fields for editing MIME type attributes - 
	enabling file extensions, style sheets, text extractors, icons and viewers to be associated with the MIME type.</p>
	
	<p>EQUELLA file types associated with this MIME type will be displayed using the configured tools and templates.</p>
	
	<ul>
		<li><b>Details</b> &mdash; <a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreDetailsEdit'')">More on editing MIME type Details...</a></li>
		<li><b>Viewers</b> &mdash; MIME type viewers are used to display the files associated with this MIME type. 
			These fields are used to select the default viewer and configure any other available viewers. 
			These viewers are displayed as options when files appear in search result lists.  
			<a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreViewersEdit'')">More on editing MIME type Viewers...</a></li>
		<li><b>Embedding Template</b> &mdash; An embedding template is used to display the item in HTML pages.  
			The template provides HTML tags and item metadata (information) for display of files associated with the MIME type.</li>
	</ul>
	
	<br>
	<h3>Other page features</h3>
	 		 
	<ul>
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreNavigation'')">More about the Navigation menu...</a></li>
	</ul>
	<div style="clear: both;"></div>
</div>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key="moreDetailsEdit">
<![CDATA[
<div id="moreDetailsEdit" style="display:none;">
	<h3>More on editing MIME type Details</h3>
	
	<p>To edit MIME type Details:</p>
		
	<ul>
		<li>Enter a description in the Description field for display with search result information.</li>
		<li>Enter or modify the MIME type.  Care should be used in modifying this field 
			to avoid unintentionally creating a new or duplicate MIME type.</li>
		<li>Enter a file extension in the Extensions field then select the ADD button 
			to associate a new file type with this MIME type.</li>
		<li>Select the <input type="button" class="button" value="Browse"> button to display the Choose File to Upload dialog then choose a new icon file then select the Open button.  
			To complete editing the icon, select the <input type="button" class="button" value="Upload"> button.</li>
		<li>Select the <input type="button" class="button" value="Save"> button to store the modified fields, or select the <input type="button" class="button" value="Cancel"> button to discard any modified fields
			and return to the MIME type editor page.</li>
	</ul>
	
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key="moreViewersEdit">
<![CDATA[
<div id="moreViewersEdit" style="display:none;">
	<h3>More on editing MIME type Viewers</h3>
	
	<p>To edit MIME type viewers:</p>
	
	<ul>
		<li>Select the Default radio button for the required viewer.</li>
		<li>Check the Enabled checkbox to enable any required viewers.</li>
		<li>Select the <input type="button" class="button" value="Configure"> button to display the Configure viewer dialog where further options are provided. 
			<a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreConfigureViewerEdit'')">More on the Configure viewer dialog...</a>
		</li>
		
	</ul>
	
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>

</div>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key="moreConfigureViewerEdit">
<![CDATA[
<div id="moreConfigureViewerEdit" style="display:none;">
	<h3>More on the Configure viewer dialog</h3>
	
	<ul>
		<li>Check the Open in new window checkbox to display files selected from the results list in a new window for this viewer.</li>
		<li>Check the Use fancybox checkbox to display the file with a wide border.</li>
		<li>Enter the width of the viewer. When the number is followed by a percentage sign (i.e. %) the width is a percentage of the screen resolution otherwise the width is interpreted as pixels.</li>
		<li>Enter a number for the height of the viewer. When the number is followed by a percentage sign (i.e. %) the height is a percentage of the screen resolution otherwise the height is interpreted as pixels.</li>
		<li>Check the Append SSO token checkbox to append a single sign on (SSO) token to the end of the resource URL.</li>
		<li>Select the OK button to save the viewer configuration and close the dialog, otherwise select the <input type="button" class="button" value="Cancel"> button to discard any changes and close the dialog.</li>
	</ul>
	
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreViewersEdit'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>
]]>
</entry>

</properties>