<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<entry key="main"><![CDATA[
<div id="main" >
<h3>My resources</h3>

<p>The My resources page provides access to all resources that you own or share. 
Resources are categorised by status with each category being displayed on a different page that 
can be accessed using the links immediately below the page title. 
<a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreCategories'')">More about categories...</a></p>

<p>A list of resources is displayed that match the categorisation criteria. 
Select the title of a listed resource to view the resource. 	
<a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreListed'')">More about listed resources...</a></p>

<p>Use the Add search to favourites or Share search query buttons to save or share the resource list.</p>

<p>Use the Sort and Filter portlets to order or reduce the number of resources displayed.</p>

<ul>
	<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreAddSearchFavorites'')">More about Add search to favourites...</a></li>
	<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreShare'')">More about Share search query...</a></li>
</ul>
<div style="clear: both;"></div>
<br>
<h3>Other page features</h3>
 		 
<ul>
	<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreNavigation'')">More about the Navigation menu...</a></li>
	<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreSortBox'')">More about the Sort box...</a></li>
	<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreFilterBox'')">More about the Filter box...</a></li>
</ul>
<div style="clear: both;"></div>
</div>
]]>
</entry>
<entry key="moreCategories">
<![CDATA[
<div id="moreCategories" style="display:none;">
<h3>More about categories</h3>

<p>The resource categories are displayed as a series of links immediately below the page title. 
Select a link to view a results list of the associated resources.</p>

<p>The available categories can include:</p>

<ul>
	<li><b>Published</b> &mdash; select this link to display a list of resources that are available to configured users of EQUELLA.</li>
	<li><b>Drafts</b> &mdash; select this link to display a list of resources that have been saved as a draft for further editing.</li>
	<li><b>Scrapbook</b> &mdash; select this link to display a list of personal resources that are not available to other users.</li>
	<li><b>Moderation queue</b> &mdash; select this link to display a list of resources that are currently in a moderation workflow.</li>
	<li><b>Archive</b> &mdash; select this link to display a list of your resources that have been archived.</li>
	<li><b>All resources</b> &mdash; select this link to display an uncategorised list of all your resources.</li>
</ul>

<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>

</div>
]]>
</entry>
<entry key="moreListed">
<![CDATA[
<div id="moreListed" style="display:none;">
<h3>More about listed resources</h3>

<p>A list of resources is displayed that match the categorisation criteria. Select the title of a listed resource to view the resource.
Search results can be displayed in groups of 10, 50 or 100 per page, with paging displayed at the end of the search results page. 
</p>

<p>The information displayed for each match comprises:</p>

<ul>
	<li><b>Resource title</b> &mdash; select this link to display the resource summary page.</li>
	<li><b>Status</b> &mdash; displays the resource status and when it was last updated.</li>
	<li><b>&lt;x> comments</b> &mdash; select this link to display the resource summary page where comments and ratings can be entered.</li>
	<li><b>Add to favourites</b> &mdash; select this link to add the resource to the favourites list.</li>
	<li><b>Remove from favourites</b> &mdash; select this link to remove the resource from your favourites list. 
	This link is only displayed for resources that have been added to your favourites list.</li>
</ul>

<ul>
<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreAddItemFavourites'')">More about Add/Remove favourites...</a></li>
</ul>
<div style="clear: both;"></div>
<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>

</div>
]]>
</entry>
<entry key="moreAddItemFavourites">
<![CDATA[
<div id="moreAddItemFavourites" style="display:none">
<h3>More about Add/Remove favourites</h3> 

<p>Resources can be added to your Favourites page for quick access.</p>

<ul>
	<li><b>Add to favourites</b> &mdash; select this link to display the Add to favourites dialog where tags can be entered to simplify searching. Select the resource version to display in the favourites page:
		<ul>
			<li><b>Always use latest version</b> &mdash; select this option to use the latest version when the current version is superseded.</li>
			<li><b>This version</b> &mdash; select this option to use this version even when later versions are available.</li>
		</ul>
	</li>
	<li>Select ADD to add to your favourites resources list and return to the resource summary or CANCEL to return to the resource summary without creating a favourite.</li>
	<li><b>Remove from favourites</b> &mdash; select this link then OK to confirm, to remove this resource from your favourites resources list.</li>
</ul>

<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>

</div>
]]>
</entry>
<entry key="moreAddSearchFavourites">
<![CDATA[
<div id="moreAddSearchFavorites" style="display:none;">
<h3>More about Add search to favourites</h3>

<p>Searches can be saved for future use by adding them to the <b>Favourites</b> page.</p>
<ul>
	<li><b>Add search to favourites</b> &mdash; select this button to display the <b>Add search to favourites</b> dialog where a name must be entered to help identify the search. 
	Select <b>ADD</b> to save the search or <b>CANCEL</b> to discard the search and return to the search results page.</li>
</ul>

<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>

</div>
]]>
</entry>
<entry key="moreShare">
<![CDATA[
	<div id="moreShare" style="display:none;">
<h3>More about Share search query</h3>

<p>Users can be emailed a resource access link or notified when the resource becomes publicly available.</p>

<ul>
<li><b>Share with others</b> &mdash; select this button to display the Share with others page where resource access or notifications can be configured.</li>
</ul>
 
<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>

</div>
]]>
</entry>
<entry key="moreNavigation">
<![CDATA[
<div id="moreNavigation" style="display:none;">
<h3>More about the Navigation menu</h3>

<p>The navigation menu is displayed on the left-hand side of the page and displays links for accessing and managing content. The menu comprises standard EQUELLA, browse, custom and administration links.
The links displayed depend on the privileges granted by the System Administrator.</p>

<ul> 
	<li><b>Standard links</b> &mdash; links for accessing content and can include Dashboard, Favourites, Search, My resources, Contribute.</li>
	<li><b>Browse links</b> &mdash; links for browsing EQUELLA topics. When more than five topics have been added the first four plus a <b>More...</b> link are displayed.</li>
	<li><b>Custom links</b> &mdash; links for commonly accessed content that can be within EQUELLA or an external website.</li>
	<li><b>Administration links</b> &mdash; links for managing or configuring EQUELLA that can include Tasks, Manage resources, Manage activations, Reporting, Settings.
	Select a navigation menu link to display the corresponding page.</li>
</ul>
 
<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>

</div>
]]>
</entry>
<entry key="moreSortBox">
<![CDATA[
<div id="moreSortBox" style="display:none;">
<h3>More about the Sort box</h3>

<p>The Sort box provides options for sorting results lists. Select the <img src="{1}"> toggle button to maximise or minimise the box.</p>

<ul>
	<li><b>Sort results by</b> &mdash; select an option from the drop-down list to change the sort order.</li>
	<li><b>Reverse order of results</b> &mdash; check this checkbox to reverse the default sort order e.g. reverses a Title ordering from A-Z to Z-A.</li>
</ul>

<!--
<ul>
	<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreSearch'')">More about searching...</a></li>
</ul>
<div style="clear: both;"></div>
 -->

<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>

</div>
]]>
</entry>
<entry key="moreFilterBox">
<![CDATA[
<div id="moreFilterBox" style="display:none;">
<h3>More about the Filter box</h3>

<p>The filter box provides options for reducing the number of displayed results. Select the <img src="{1}"> toggle button to maximise or minimise the box.
Multiple filters can be appliedand can include the following filters:</p>

<ul>
	<li><b>Filter by keyword</b> &mdash; enter a keyword then select the <b>SEARCH</b> button to reduce the display to matching results.</li>
	<li><b>Filter by collection</b> &mdash; select an option from the drop-down list to only display results from the selected collection.</li>
	<!--
	<li><b>Filter by status</b> &mdash; select an option from the drop-down list to display results with the selected status.</li>
	<li><b>Filter by owner</b> &mdash; select the <b>SELECT USER</b> button to display the <b>Select owner to filter by</b> dialog where owners can be found by name search then selected to filter the search results. Select the CHANGE USER button to change the owner selected or select the CLEAR button to remove.</li>
	-->
	<li><b>Filter by date modified</b> &mdash; select an option from the drop-down list then enter or select a date. Select <b>Clear</b> to remove the date filter.</li>
	<li><b>Filter by resource type</b> &mdash; select a checkbox to display only matching resources.</li>
	<!--
	<li><b>Filter by assignment</b> &mdash; select an option from the drop-down list to only display results with the selected user assignment. Check <b>Only show tasks that I must moderate</b> to display tasks that you must moderate.</li>
	<li><b>Filter by course</b> &mdash; select the <b>SELECT COURSE</b> button to display the <b>Select a course</b> dialog where courses can be found by name search then selected to filter the search results.</li>
	<li><b>Activation range</b> &mdash; enter or select a date for end date, start date and activated to filter results. Select <b>Clear</b> to remove the date filter.</li>
	<li><b>Filter by type</b> &mdash; select an option from the drop-down list to display results with the selected type.</li>
	<li><b>Filter by visibility</b> &mdash; select an option from the drop-down list to display results with the selected visibility.</li>
	-->	
</ul>
 
<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''main'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>

</div>
]]>
</entry>
<entry key="myresourceseditorhelp">
<![CDATA[
<div id="myresourcesMain">
	<h3>Edit My resources portlet</h3>
	<p>The <b>My resources</b> portlet displays resources you have created or categorised by their moderation status.<p>
	
	<p>To configure the portlet:</p>
	
	<ul>
		<li><b>Title</b> &mdash; enter the portlet name displayed in the portlet title bar.</li>
		<li>Select save to create the portlet and display it on the <b>Dashboard</b>.</li>
		<li>Select cancel to discard any entered information and return to the <b>Dashboard</b>.</li>
	</ul>
	<br>
	
	<h3>Other page features</h3>
	<ul>
		{0}
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreNavigation'')">More about the Navigation menu...</a></li>
	</ul>
	<div style="clear: both;"></div>
</div>
]]>
</entry>
<entry key="commonmoredivs">
<![CDATA[
<div id="moreNavigation" style="display: none">
	<h3>More about the Navigation menu</h3>
	<p>The navigation menu is displayed on the left-hand side of the page and displays links for accessing and managing content. The menu comprises standard EQUELLA, browse, custom and administration links.
	The links displayed depend on the privileges granted by the System Administrator.</p>
	<ul> 
		<li><b>Standard links</b> &mdash; links for accessing content and can include Dashboard, Favourites, Search, My resources, Contribute.</li>
		<li><b>Browse links</b> &mdash; links for browsing EQUELLA topics. When more than five topics have been added the first four plus a <b>More...</b> link are displayed.</li>
		<li><b>Custom links</b> &mdash; links for commonly accessed content that can be within EQUELLA or an external website.</li>
		<li><b>Administration links</b> &mdash; links for managing or configuring EQUELLA that can include Tasks, Manage resources, Manage activations, Reporting, Settings.
		Select a navigation menu link to display the corresponding page.</li>
	</ul>
	
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''myresourcesMain'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>

</div>

<div id="moreAdministrators" style="display: none">
	<h3>Further information for portlet administrators</h3>
	<p>The following controls are only displayed to portlet administrators:</p>
	<ul>
		<li><b>Disabled</b> &mdash; disables the portlet and removes it from the <b>Dashboard</b>.</li>
		<li><b>Show for other users</b> &mdash check this checkbox to add this portlet to every user’s dashboard and enable the options:
		<ul>
			<li><b>Users can close</b> &mdash check this checkbox to allow users to remove the portlet from their dashboard.</li>
			<li><b>Users can minimise</b> &mdash check this checkbox to allow users to reduce the portlet to its title bar.</li>
			<li><b>Visible to</b> &mdash select the <b>CHANGE...</b> button to restrict the portlet to selected users, roles or groups. The selected users, roles or groups are displayed.</li>
		</ul>
		</li>
	</ul>
		
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''myresourcesMain'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>
]]>
</entry>
</properties>