<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<entry key="tasksportleteditorhelp"><![CDATA[
<div id="tasksMain" >
	<h3>Edit Tasks portlet</h3>
	<p>The <b>Tasks</b> portlet displays all outstanding moderation tasks assigned to you directly or to any associated user groups or roles.<p>
	
	<p>To configure the portlet:</p>
	
	<ul>
		<li><b>Title</b> &mdash; enter the portlet name displayed in the portlet title bar.</li>
		<li>Select save to create the portlet and display it on the <b>Dashboard</b>.</li>
		<li>Select cancel to discard any entered information and return to the <b>Dashboard</b>.</li>
	</ul>
	<br>
	
	<h3>Other page features</h3>
	<ul>
		{0}
		<li style="float: left"><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''moreNavigation'')">More about the Navigation menu...</a></li>
	</ul>
	<div style="clear: both;"></div>
</div>
]]>
</entry>

<entry key="commonportletmoredivs"><![CDATA[
<div id="moreNavigation" style="display: none">
	<h3>More about the Navigation menu</h3>
	<p>The navigation menu is displayed on the left-hand side of the page and displays links for accessing and managing content. The menu comprises standard EQUELLA, browse, custom and administration links.
	The links displayed depend on the privileges granted by the System Administrator.</p>
	<ul> 
		<li><b>Standard links</b> &mdash; links for accessing content and can include Dashboard, Favourites, Search, My resources, Contribute.</li>
		<li><b>Browse links</b> &mdash; links for browsing EQUELLA topics. When more than five topics have been added the first four plus a <b>More...</b> link are displayed.</li>
		<li><b>Custom links</b> &mdash; links for commonly accessed content that can be within EQUELLA or an external website.</li>
		<li><b>Administration links</b> &mdash; links for managing or configuring EQUELLA that can include Tasks, Manage resources, Manage activations, Reporting, Settings.
		Select a navigation menu link to display the corresponding page.</li>
	</ul>
	
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''tasksMain'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>

</div>

<div id="moreAdministrators" style="display: none">
	<h3>Further information for portlet administrators</h3>
	<p>The following controls are only displayed to portlet administrators:</p>
	<ul>
		<li><b>Disabled</b> &mdash; disables the portlet and removes it from the <b>Dashboard</b>.</li>
		<li><b>Show for other users</b> &mdash check this checkbox to add this portlet to every user’s dashboard and enable the options:
		<ul>
			<li><b>Users can close</b> &mdash check this checkbox to allow users to remove the portlet from their dashboard.</li>
			<li><b>Users can minimise</b> &mdash check this checkbox to allow users to reduce the portlet to its title bar.</li>
			<li><b>Visible to</b> &mdash select the <b>CHANGE...</b> button to restrict the portlet to selected users, roles or groups. The selected users, roles or groups are displayed.</li>
		</ul>
		</li>
	</ul>
		
	<p><a href="javascript:void(0)" onclick="switchText(''tasksMain'')"><b>Back</b></a></p>
</div>
]]>
</entry>
</properties>
